withfriendship.com 2015-03-19

# Privacy Policy - Withfriendship.com

Following describes privacy practices specific to Withfriendship.com. 

### Personal Information

  1. **Browsing Withfriendship.com** You can watch videos on Withfriendship.com without having a Withfriendship.com Account. 
  2. **Your Withfriendship.com Account.** For some activities on Withfriendship.com, like uploading videos, posting comments, slides, jokes, quotes you need a Withfriendship.com Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. 
  3. **Usage Information.** When you use Withfriendship.com, we may record information about your usage of the site, such as friends, favourites you subscribe to, which other users you communicate with, the videos you watch, the frequency and size of data transfers, and information you display about yourself as well as information you click on in Withfriendship.com (including UI elements, settings). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your Withfriendship.com Account. 
  4. **Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g., video comments, your profile page) may be collected and used by others.
  5. If you submit personal information to Withfriendship.com, we may use that information to operate, maintain, and improve the features and functionality of Withfriendship.com, and to process communications you send to us.
  6. We do not use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Withfriendship.com changes or for customer service purposes). 
  7. We use cookies and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Withfriendship.com; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

### Information That is Publicly Available

  1. When you create a Withfriendship.com Account, some information about your Withfriendship.com Account profile without the email address will be provided to other users of Withfriendship.com. 
  2. Your Withfriendship.com Account name, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on Withfriendship.com, such as when you upload videos or send messages through Withfriendship.com. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site.
  3. Any videos that you submit to Withfriendship.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by other Withfriendship.com users or the general public. 
  4. You may also choose to add personal information which may include your name, gender, profile picture or other details, that will be visible to other users on your Withfriendship.com Account profile page. If you choose to add certain features to your Withfriendship.com Account profile page, then these features and your activity associated with these features will be displayed to other users and may be aggregated and shared with your friends or other users. Such shared activity may include your favorite videos, videos you rated and videos that you have uploaded.

### Your Choices

  1. If you have a Withfriendship.com Account, you may update or correct your personal profile information, email preferences and privacy settings at any time by visiting your account profile page. 
  2. You may control the information that is available to other users and your confirmed friends at any time by editing your Withfriendship.com Account and the features that are included on your profile page.
  3. You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through Withfriendship.com, in which case you can still view videos and explore Withfriendship.com, but Withfriendship.com may not be able to provide certain services to you. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them.

### More Information

Withfriendship.com adheres to the law of Government of India privacy principles.   
For more information about our privacy practices write to us at: [privacy@withfriendship.com](mailto:privacy@withfriendship.com "Send Email")   
Withfriendship.com Privacy Policy 

HIOXINDIA,  
No.7A-F, Ganesha Complex campus,  
N.K.Palayam Road,  
Singanallur,  
Coimbatore,  
Tamilnadu, INDIA.  
PinCode - 641005.
